ic-on-line.cn 2018-10-25

# JiTong MCU And EPROM Sales Parts List --- IC-ON-LINE

|   
---  
  
Our website list :  [www.datasheet.hk] [www.maxim4u.com] [www.ic-on-line.cn] [www.ic-on-line.com] [www.ic-on-line.net] [www.alldatasheet.com.cn] [www.gdcy.com] [www.gdcy.net] [www.iczj.com]   
  
At our site we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important.   
This privacy policy document explains what personal information we collect and how we use that information.   
**1\. Data Collected**  
  
When you visit our website or use our service, information about your visit, such as your browser type, your IP address, the page served are passively collected by our system, The collection may be implemented by third parties or our partners. 

This information is generally collected using the web cookies, hyperlinks that contain web or pixels (beacons). Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier ,Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. You can set your browser to disable or delete those cookies.

The following are types of cookies and its purpose. We do not use the collected information to identify you without your consent. 

**Performance Cookies**

Performance Cookies collect anonymized information about how you use the Sites. For example, these Cookies may tell us which pages you go to most often and if you receive error messages from our web pages. We use this information to improve how our Sites work. By using our Sites, you agree we can place these cookies on your device.

**Functionality Cookies**

Functionality Cookies allow our website to remember the choices you make, such as your login information (if any), preferred language or region you are in, and can provide enhanced, more personal features. These Cookies can also be used to remember changes you made to text size, fonts and other parts of Sites pages you can customize. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these Cookies collect may be anonymized, and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites. By using our Sites, you agree we can place these Cookies on your device.

**Advertising Cookies**

These Cookies collect information to deliver you more relevant advertising. They may be placed by us, by third parties acting on our behalf, or by advertising networks with our permission. They remember other websites you have visited, and advertising networks may share this information with others including advertisers. By using our Sites, you agree we can place these Cookies on your device.  
  
**2\. Use of Data**  
  
We use the collected data for various purposes:

To provide and maintain our Service  
To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service  
To monitor the usage of our Service  
To detect, prevent and address technical issues  
To help our advertising effort, using anonymous personal data  
  
**3\. Retention of Data**  
  
Generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.  

**4\. Security Of Data**  
  
The security of your Data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we make the best & reasonable efforts to protect your Data, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your data transmitted through our website.  

**5\. Consent**  
  
By using the Site, you accept the terms of this Privacy Policy and consent to our collection, use, disclosure and retention of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. You also consent to the use of cookies, beacons and information by us and by the third parties mentioned in this privacy policy. 

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY PART OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE.

If you have any questions or suggestions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [ ioldatasheet@gmail.com](mailto:ioldatasheet@gmail.com) .  
  
**6\. Update**  
  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Tuesday, May 22th, 2018.  
Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here.
